# Robert Lee Brown

6654 Densmore Ave. Van Nuys, CA 91406 904.323.8479 robert.lee.bush@gmail.com

#### Profile

With my ten plus years repairing consumer electronics, sound, lighting and versus types of music equipment, My strong technical skillset and high energy make, problem-solving easy for me. I also have more than thirteen years as an entertainer, music performer, and producer. Which has taught me to be patient and understanding? The skills I have learned over the years have helped me see patterns to solve every day electronic issues. My experience makes me a well rounded and strong team player.

#### Experience

Apple hardware engineer / Repair Tech | Unitek Computer Store - May/2018

- · Apple Hardware repair specialists
- · I work at both locations do to my ability to repair devices quickly
- · Diagnostics and troubleshooting hardware and software
- · iPhone /iPad and other phones and Tablet troubleshooting and repair.
- Repair damaged and or, custom build Laptop and Computers.

## General Manager/ Lead Tech, Ubreakifix - 12/2013 - 9/2017

- · Manage the purchasing of inventory and stock.
- · Oversee daily operations for the business.
- · Coordinate the development of key performance goals create reports.
- · Oversee key hiring and training of new employees.
- · Repair damaged and or build electronic consumer devices.

## Sales Representative | Repair Technician, Sprint - 11/2012 - 12/2013

- Customer retention by performing all aspects of customer service, including answering phone system, advising customers of promotions, and providing detailed information on various products.
- Resolved billing questions and disputes while providing technical support for all cell phones and wireless devices.
- Handled inbound sales duties, exceeding sales goals by 150%.
- Lead sales representative in store for Samsung devices.

# Installer/Tech | Classroom technology solutions- 11/2011 - 12/2012

- · Setup and installed projectors, smart boards
- Installed and replaced Cat 5 and Cat 6 cables
- · Built remotes for custom tv tuners and IR sensors

### Sales Representative | Geek Squad, Best Buy - 11/2006 - 8/2011

- Traveled with the Project Team installing all product displays and demo units in new Best Buy stores across the USA.
- Provided thorough support and problem resolution for customers.
- · On-site computer repair, troubleshooting, and product installations in customer homes.

• Displayed courtesy and strong interpersonal skills with all customer interactions.

Administrative Assistant, Xpel Muzik – 11/2010 - 7/2011

- Planned and supervised all personal travel arrangements including air travel, ground transportation, and accommodations.
- · Writing letters and emails on behalf of other office staff.
- · Relying on email, telephone or face to face inquiries.
- Maintained purchases, gifts, invitations, thank you cards, and any expenses.

Education

A. Philip Randolph Academies of Technology — High School Diploma, 2000-2004

Skills Microsoft Office (Word, Powerpoint, Outlook, Excel), Windows and Mac OS proficient, Knowledgable of video, lighting, and sound equipment, PC, Mobile, all Apple devices and other consumer electronics.